[
    {
        "question": "1+1",
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "2+2",
        "answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "/3+3",
        "answer": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "6+6",
        "answer": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "10+5",
        "answer": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "10+10",
        "answer": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "10+15",
        "answer": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "30+3",
        "answer": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "30+15",
        "answer": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "25+25",
        "answer": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "30+30",
        "answer": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "30+35 ",
        "answer": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "33+33 ",
        "answer": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "35+35",
        "answer": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "40+40",
        "answer": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "50+50",
        "answer": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "100+5",
        "answer": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "100+10",
        "answer": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "100+20",
        "answer": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "100+30",
        "answer": "130"
    }
]